<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Warner's Blog]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Steve Warner's Blog]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/stvwrnr/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 21:36:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/stvwrnr/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Snowdon by MTB bike for EACH]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Snowdon by MTB bike for EACH</h1><p>We rode up Snowdon by MTB bikes for EACH (East Anglian Children's Hospices). Due to the weather (55mph wind and low visibility) etc, we didn't make the summit (0.5mile away), so we are returning in 2014 to make it all the way.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9199184beb4f3b9c96649981234971207daa4e2a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/78435775</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">50db47a0-0fdf-4ac1-90d0-a250fd562972</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 21:35:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OpenMTB – the new UK access organisation  ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>OpenMTB – the new UK access organisation  </h1><p>Stepping out of the shadows is a new, British mountain bike access organisation. It’s made up of volunteers from several different corners of mountain biking in the UK – there are access officers, advocacy representatives from organisations such at British Cycling and the CTC, as well as journalists, IMBA (remember them?) and trail-building organisations throughout the UK.  The formation of a national body to represent mountain bikers has been made more pressing by the recent Welsh Government consultation on access to land in Wales, but many riders are finding that, without a strong local group, like RideSheffield, there isn’t really a national body that the likes of local councils and National Parks can talk to about trail access. Hence the formation of OpenMTB.  There’s a Facebook group and you can follow @openmtb on Twitter (though there’s nothing to see at the moment). Knowing some of the people on the panel (who will, presumably, introduce themselves shortly, rather than remaining a shadowy organisation like U.N.C.L.E.) we have high hopes that they will carry both the needs of mountain bikers and the Government-facing authority to actually get things done in our name.    Here’s what OpenMTB (not to be confused with the mountain bike brand, Open) has to say about itself:  “Early in 2015 representatives from a number of mountain bike associations met journalists and industry experts from across England and Wales to see how we could work together for the benefit of our community.  In the past it has been difficult for governing bodies to consult our diverse community due to the lack of a single point of contact. OpenMTB has been formed to act co-operatively on behalf of our supporters – locally, regionally and nationally on issues that concern our supporters. These issues include improved access rights, user group consultations, trail improvement and maintenance etc.  We have agreed how we will work in partnership with cycling’s main bodies. By using existing relationships with our supporters and the campaigning experience and organisational skills of CTC and British Cycling we aim to work in a positive manner to bring about real benefits for the off-road cycling community. The group already have links with National Park Authorities, the Forestry Commission and other land managers and will continue to build on these in the future.  Current rights of way were created before the mountain bike was invented and we believe the system needs a thorough review in order to reflect current patterns of recreational use. Scotland has undergone such a review and is seeing the benefits modernisation brings. User groups are equal and are bound by a single responsible access code. Using such a code we seek to bring access rights up to date across the UK.  In our first campaign OpenMTB, CTC, British Cycling and Welsh Cycling will soon be launching ‘Trails for Wales’ which focuses on the current Welsh Government consultation for increased access in Wales. We feel that modernising the Welsh access system is a sensible step towards a fair system across the whole of the UK.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://singletrackworld.com/2015/08/openmtb-the-new-uk-access-organisation/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1f2b0058-e356-4c20-ab78-6ce4a86e9738</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 21:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Danny MacAskill - Cascadia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Danny MacAskill - Cascadia</h1><p>Join Danny MacAskill on an insane journey across the rooftops of Gran Canaria. Mixing vertigo-inducing lines and killer POV-footage, "Cascadia" delivers some incredible riding. In collaboration with Mount Creative http://www.mountcreative.com/ and Vision Ramps http://visionramps.co.uk/ A Special Thanks to the wonderful people of Gran Canaria who opened their homes to us and helped make this project a reality.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ea7038715e5f0b56ae7ff929ba06a51db8920eda.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GL0rbxB9Lqg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d4efc426-867e-4799-8fe1-257276ce20e5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 16:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Trail to Kazbegi]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Trail to Kazbegi</h1><p>Experience the feature story: features.bikemag.com/kazbegi/ What happens when four like-minded adventurers head into one of the world's wildest mountain ranges with nothing but their mountain bikes and enough food to survive for 10 days? The answer? What doesn't happen? Terrifying lightning storms. Raging-river crossings. Snow-covered glacial pass traverses. Mind-melting descents.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/629fb63848f479911eedb294fe54a112b66aa44b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WFIrHgleSxs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a64a9e3e-8379-4f2a-a3f1-c178d49b2da4</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 16:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>